Finding Aid for the Walter J. Harrelson Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Walter J. Harrelson Papers
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0192
47.50 linear_feet
- EMML – Budget, 8/31/82-8/31/94 (Box 1)
- Sergew Hable Sellassie and Tedla Tebeje- AdvancesSergew Hable Sellassie and Tedla Tebeje- Advances (Box 1)
- EMML, 6/1/77 – 8/31/79 (Box 1)
- EMML Budget (Box 1)
- Ford Foundation Ethiopian Manuscripts (Box 1)
- NEH – H 6356 Revised Pull Sheets/Accounting (Box 1)
- Unlabeled- (Travel Expense Materials) (Box 1)
- Booklet – An Ethiopian Manuscript Microfilming Program (Box 1)
- NEH –H 6356 Revised (Box 1)
- Unlabeled- (EMML Materials) (Box 1)
- EMML –4902 – 4225 from, 9/1/74-8/31/75 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, 1974 -1975 (Box 1)
- EMML – Advances (Box 1)
- EMML 4903-4225 from, 7/1/76-8/31/77 (Box 1)
- EMML- Minutes - Collegeville, MN, 12/28/77-12/29/77 (Box 1)
- EMML- Meeting - Collegeville, MN, 12/28/77-12/29/77 (Box 1)
- Loose- Hill Monastic Manuscript Library- Notes on Meeting, 11/15/77 (Box 1)
- Loose- NEH Grant Application (Box 1)
- Loose- NEH Grant Application Guidelines for Publication Program (Box 1)
- Harrelson Grant Proposal to Mellon Foundation (Box 1)
- Clip Folder- 4903 – 4225 from 7/1/76-8/31/77 VU Accounting Pull Sheets (Box 2)
- Clip Folder- EMML RC-27881-77-863 6-34815 from 6/17/77-8/31/84 VU Accounting Pull Sheets (Box 2)
- Loose- VU Accounting Pull Sheets with dates from, 1/31/79- 6/30/84 (Box 2)
- 4 Copies- A Catalogue of Ethiopian Manuscripts Microfilmed for EMML and MMML Vol. 1 (Box 2)
- 3 Copies- A Catalogue of Ethiopian Manuscripts Microfilmed for EMML and MMML Vol. 2 (Box 2)
- 8th International Conference of Ethiopian Studies- 25th Anniversary Institute of Ethiopian Studies, 11/26/84-11/30/84 (Box 3)
- Loose- Papers Presented to the 8th International Conference of Ethiopian Studies (Box 3)
- Loose- Papers Presented to the United Bible Societies Translation Workshop at Stuttgart, 5/15/84-5/26/84 (Box 3)
- Year End Report of the United Bible Societies Nov., 1984 (Box 3)
- Bulletin of Ethiopian Manuscripts - Vol. IX Nos. 1,2,3,and 4 (Box 3)
- Bulletin of Ethiopian Manuscripts - Vol. X Nos. 1,2,3,and 4 (Box 3)
- Bulletin of Ethiopian Manuscripts - Vol. XI Nos. 1,3,and 4 (Box 3)
- Bulletin of Ethiopian Manuscripts - Vol. XII No. 1 (Box 3)
- 5Copies- An Ethiopian Manuscript Microfilming Program (Box 3)
- Ford Foundation- Ethiopian Trip (Box 3)
- Walter Harrelson Notebook- 1986- Notes (35 Pages) (Box 3)
- Ethiopia (Box 3)
- Ford Foundation Consulting Papers (Box 3)
- Ethiopia, August 9-21 (Box 3)
- EMML- Ford Grant (Box 3)
- Ethiopia Microfilming (Box 3)
- Ethiopia, November 1984 (Box 3)
- NEH- Ethiopia Project- Final Report (Box 3)
- Vatican Ethiopian College (Box 3)
- Ethiopia Trip, 10/15/82-10/24/82 (Box 3)
- EMML – Budget (Box 3)
- EMML- Project Report (Box 3)
- EMML- Current (Box 3)
- Apostles Association- Ethiopia (Box 3)
- EMML- Ford Proposal (Box 3)
- 5 Copies- A Catalogue of Ethiopian Manuscripts Microfilmed for the EMML, Addis Ababa and for the Hill Monastic Manuscript Library, Collegeville, MN – Vol. II (Box 4)
- 1 Copy- A Catalogue of Ethiopian Manuscripts Microfilmed for the EMML, Addis Ababa and for the Hill Monastic Manuscript Library, Collegeville, MN – Vol. V (Box 4)
- 1 Copy- A Catalogue of Ethiopian Manuscripts Microfilmed for the EMML, Addis Ababa and for the Hill Monastic Manuscript Library, Collegeville, MN – Vol. VI (Box 4)
- 4 Copies- A Catalogue of Ethiopian Manuscripts Microfilmed for the EMML, Addis Ababa and for the Hill Monastic Manuscript Library, Collegeville, MN – Vol. VII (Box 4)
- Pseudepigrapha Group, SBL (Box 5)
- Pseudepigrapha Dictionary (Box 5)
- Pseudepigrapha Seminar (Box 5)
- Pseudepigrapha Correspondence (Box 5)
- Pseudepigrapha Scholars at work (Box 5)
- Pseudepigrapha Materials – Documents (Box 5)
- Pseudepigrapha Correspondence, Seminar, and Project Members (Box 5)
- Pseudepigrapha Steering Committee (Box 5)
- Minutes- Pseudepigrapha Project, 1969, 1970, 1971 (Box 5)
- Paper – Test of Joseph, 7/1/75 (Box 5)
- RSV- General (Box 6)
- RSV- General Correspondence (Box 6)
- RSV- Revision (Box 6)
- RSV- Advertising Committee (Box 6)
- RSV- Committee- Minutes (Box 6)
- RSV- Apocrypha (Box 6)
- Tiqqune Sopherim (Box 6)
- RSV-Topical Division- Burrows (Box 6)
- RSV- NT Materials (Box 6)
- RSV-Guidelines- Composite (Box 6)
- RSV- Changes Approved to, 1978 (Box 6)
- Footnotes, Verse Numbers (Box 6)
- RSV- Flora, Fauna (Box 6)
- RSV, December 11-15 (Box 6)
- Loose- RSV Materials (relating to Index) (Box 6)
- Deuteronomy (Box 6)
- Exodus (Box 6)
- Numbers (Box 6)
- Nehemiah Review (Box 6)
- Ezra- RSV (Box 6)
- Psalms (Box 6)
- Tantur, 3/17/83-/3/23/83 (Box 6)
- Tantur- Consortium Idea (Box 6)
- Interfaith Academy of Peace, Jerusalem (Box 6)
- Tantur- Advisory Council, 1982 (Box 6)
- Tantur- Advisory Council (Box 6)
- January 1986 Exodus Agenda (Box 7)
- RSV- Leviticus (Box 7)
- Numbers (Box 7)
- Deuteronomy (Box 7)
- Joshua (Box 7)
- Judges (Box 7)
- Ruth (Box 7)
- 2 Samuel (Box 7)
- 1-2 Samuel Notes (Box 7)
- 1 Samuel, DSS (Box 7)
- 1-2 Kings, RSV (Box 7)
- RSV- Exodus (Box 7)
- 1-2 Kings (Box 7)
- 2 Chronicles (Box 7)
- 11 Samuel, 1&2 Kings for Comparison with Chronicles (Box 7)
- 1-2 Chronicles Agenda (Box 7)
- Jan 1986- 2 Chronicles Agenda (Box 7)
- Ezra (Box 7)
- Nehemiah (Box 7)
- Esther (Box 7)
- Job (Box 7)
- RSV- Psalms (Box 8)
- RSV- Psalms (Box 8)
- RSV- Psalms revision (Box 8)
- RSV- Proverbs (Box 8)
- Ecclesiastes (Box 8)
- Changes voted for Song of Solomon (Box 8)
- Changes voted for Hosea (Box 8)
- Joel (Box 8)
- Changes voted for Amos (Box 8)
- Obadiah voted (Box 8)
- RSV- Jonah (Box 8)
- Changes Voted for Micah (Box 8)
- Nahum (Box 8)
- Habakkuk (Box 8)
- Changes voted for Zephariah (Box 8)
- Haggai (Box 8)
- Zechariah (Box 8)
- RSV- Malachi (Box 8)
- 1 Maccabees (Box 8)
- 2 Maccabees (Box 8)
- Judith (Box 8)
- Tobit (Box 8)
- Wisdom of Solomon (Box 8)
- Sirach (Box 8)
- RSV- Notes 2 Esdras (Box 8)
- 12 Prophets- RSV (Box 8)
- RSV- Lamentations (Box 8)
- Changes voted for Ezekiel (Box 8)
- RSV- Daniel (Box 8)
- RSV- Isaiah (Box 8)
- Isaiah 46-66 (Box 8)
- Isaiah 40-66 (Box 8)
- Proverbs (Box 8)
- Lamentations (Box 8)
- Ecclesiates (Box 8)
- Nehemiah (Box 8)
- RSV- Jeremiah (Box 8)
- 4 Clip Folders- Bible Translations (Box 9)
- 1 Clip Folder- Notes on Translation (Box 9)
- Binder- Class Notes- Theology of the Hebrew Bible (Box 9)
- Binder- Class Notes- Advanced Hebrew (Box 9)
- Binder- Class Notes- Methods of the Critical Study of the Hebrew Bible (Box 9)
- Bound Notes- Israelite Faith and Culture (Box 10)
- Bound Notes- Religion and Worship of Israel (Box 10)
- Bound Notes- Amos (Box 10)
- Bound Notes- OT Prophecy (Box 10)
- Bound Notes-Zephamiah, Ezekiel, Joel, and Malachi (Box 10)
- Bound Notes- Habakkuk Notes (Box 10)
- Bound Notes-Zechariah- Hebrew (Box 10)
- Bound Notes- Prophetic Tradition I (Box 10)
- Bound Notes- Prophetic Tradition II (Box 10)
- Bound Notes- Prophetic Tradition III (Box 10)
- Bound Notes- Prophetic Tradition IV (Box 10)
- Bound Notes- SBL Paper, 1980 (Box 11)
- Bound Notes- Humanities 200 Spring, 1982 (Box 11)
- Bound Notes- Hebrew Literature (Box 11)
- Bound Notes- GE’EZ Grammar (Box 11)
- Bound Notes- Ethiopia (Box 11)
- Bound Notes- Prophets and Proclamation (Box 11)
- Bound Notes- Theology of the Hebrew Bible (Box 11)
- Bound Notes- Ugaritic Texts (Box 10)
- Bound Notes- Aramaic Papyri (Box 10)
- Bound Notes- Aramaic Readings (Box 11)
- Bound Notes- OT and Archeology (Box 11)
- Shechem I (Box 12)
- Shechem II (Box 12)
- Loose- Papers of Psalms (Box 12)
- Hebrew Poetry (Box 12)
- The Prophets and Contemporary Proclamation (Box 12)
- DSS- Seminar, Hebrew (Box 12)
- DSS- English (Box 12)
- HSV- Seminar- College (Box 12)
- Enoch- GE’EZ Manuscript (Box 12)
- Prophets- Fort Campbell (Box 12)
- Huntsville- Genesis, 1981 (Box 12)
- Advanced Hebrew (Box 12)
- Ten Commandments and Human Rights (Box 12)
- Psalms- DIV 304a (Box 12)
- Huntsville- Fall 1979 Intertestamental Literature (Box 12)
- Westminster Presbyterian Church- Psalm Course, Nov.-Dec. 1979 (Box 12)
- German Readings (Box 12)
- Religion and Library (Box 12)
- OT Theology- Systematic Approach (Box 12)
- Psalms Notes- old (Box 12)
- Yadin-The Temple Scroll (Box 12)
- W. Rudolph, Introduction to Jeremiah (Box 12)
- Milgrom- The Temple Scroll (Box 12)
- H. Kremers, Communion in Suffering with God (Box 12)
- J. Maier, Die Templerolle Vom Toten Meer (Box 12)
- W. Harrelson, Bibliography of Jeremiah (Box 12)
- A. Caquot, Le Rouleau du Temple (Box 12)
- Habakkuk (Box 12)
- Psalms- RSV Revised- Extra Copy (Box 12)
- Reviews, 1983 (Box 13)
- Mercer Dictionary Articles, 7/30/87 (Box 13)
- “Why Christians need to study the OT” (Box 13)
- Memphis- Cumberland Presbyterian Seminary and Lindenwood Christian, 10/16/88 and 10/18/88-10/19/88 (Box 13)
- “Creation” Breakfast 2/3 (Box 13)
- Article Correspondence (Box 13)
- Articles reassigned (Box 13)
- Mercer Dictionary of the Bible (Box 13)
- Names of Possible writers- Mercer Dictionary of the Bible (Box 13)
- Loose- Mercer Dictionary Materials (Box 13)
- Mercer Dictionary of the Bible- OT article assigned (Box 13)
- Assignments- Mercer Dictionary of the Bible (Box 13)
- Mercer Dictionary of the Bible Papers (Box 13)
- Mercer Dictionary of the Bible- NT, Archeology, and Apostles (Box 13)
- Mercer Dictionary of the Bible Articles Assignment computer list (Box 13)
- Scanning materials (Box 13)
- Mercer Dictionary of the Bible- Maps and Illustrations (Box 13)
- 2nd Presbyterian- Amos (Box 14)
- “Asking and Receiving” 2 Kings: 5 and Luke 11 Woodmont Christian Church (Box 14)
- Kanuga, June 1989 (Box 14)
- Wingate- Preaching Workshop 9/29 (Box 14)
- Alumni/ae Address, 5/26/89 (Box 14)
- Ester- Textual and Translation Problems (Box 14)
- Wilkinson Ordination, 6/4/89 (Box 14)
- Faithful Outsiders 6/4/89 Vine Street (Box 14)
- St. Henry’s 2/11 RF&WH, 7/30/87 (Box 14)
- UNA- Human Rights 12/9 (Box 14)
- 2/27 Keeping Faith in the Hard Times (Box 14)
- JF Alumni Dinner, 1/29/89 (Box 14)
- Preaching Workshop- Psalms, October 3 (Box 14)
- The Christian Impulse to Jewish/ Christian Relations (Box 14)
- Berquist Ordination 5/13 (Box 14)
- Faith seeking Knowledge, Knowledge seeking Faith (Box 14)
- Westminster Presbyterian Lectures (Box 14)
- Exodus Lectures- Lindenwood (Box 14)
- Baltimore- 9/29- Jewish/ Christian Relations Dinner (Box 14)
- Commencement 5/13/88- Walter Harrelson Talk (Box 14)
- Workshop 9/28- I Do Sermon (Box 14)
- Bible and Pastoral Care (Box 14)
- Jewish Christian Relations, Mar/Apr 88 (Box 14)
- Ancient Law Codes and Human Rights (Box 14)
- Psalm 8 (Box 14)
- Psalm 104 (Box 14)
- Religion in America Lecture- Civil Rights (Box 14)
- Psalm 51 (Box 14)
- Psalm 42-43 (Box 14)
- Psalm 44 (Box 14)
- Psalm 137 (Box 14)
- Psalm 90 (Box 14)
- Psalm 23 (Box 14)
- Psalm 119 (Box 14)
- 2 Samuel 23 1-7 (Box 14)
- Psalm 139 (Box 14)
- Psalm 73 (Box 14)
- Psalm 22 (Box 14)
- Psalm 130 (Box 14)
- Psalm 118 (Box 14)
- Falashas (Box 14)
- Gatlinburg, Feb 7-10 (Box 14)
- Prophets Manuscript (Box 14)
- Nahun- Anchor Bible (Box 14)
- Obadiah (Box 14)
- Obadiah and Nabum Commentary (Box 14)
- Haggai- Anchor Bible (Box 14)
- Hosea- Anchor Bible (Box 14)
- Prophecy and Public Policy- 12 Sept. Benton Chapel (Box 14)
- Peniel Ridge, Psalms (Box 14)
- University of Richmond, Psalms, 10/28-10/29 (Box 14)
- On His Shoulder- 1st Baptist (Box 14)
- Sermons, Addresses, Progress (Box 14)
- AIDS Vigil, 9/5/86-9/7/86 (Box 15)
- Bible and Inclusive Language (Box 15)
- 10/1 Belle Meade United Methodist Church (Box 15)
- Churches of Soviet Union (Box 15)
- Sept 2 Worship VDS (Box 15)
- Belmont Methodist- Psalms (Box 15)
- UNA- USA Meeting 2/24/87 (United Nations) (Box 15)
- Pursuing Interfaith Understanding- Huntsville (Box 15)
- Egypt Bible (Box 15)
- Forum Knoxville (Box 15)
- Otey Chapel- Abortion 3/22 (Box 15)
- AIDS Nov. 3 (Box 15)
- Feb. 18 Peniel Ridge “I Thou” (Box 15)
- Sewanee-Bible Translations and Translating (Box 15)
- Birmingham Study Forum 2/12 (Box 15)
- RSV Celeb., 11/2/86 (Box 15)
- The Bible on Illness (Box 15)
- Kentucky Wesleyan, Owensboro- Beavan Lectures, 10/28-10/29 (Box 15)
- South Africa and Church (Box 15)
- Houston 11/19-11/20 Alumni/ae (Box 15)
- Ten Commandments Lecture (Box 15)
- Methodist Conference, Gatlinburg, 2/16/87-2/19/87 (Box 15)
- “Disciple” Project- United Methodists, 2/17-3/23 (Box 15)
- Hutton Funeral, 7/22/87 (Box 15)
- 1st Presbyterian- Columbia 2/28 (Box 15)
- Bethany Hills- Disciples of Christ, Men’s Fellowship, 5/19- 5/20 (Box 15)
- Spirituality of Hebrew Bible (Box 15)
- Belle Meade United Methodist 2/23, 3/2, 3/9 (Box 15)
- Huntsville 2/22, 3/1, 3/8, 3/15 (Box 15)
- 2/29 Homosexuality and the Bible (Box 15)
- Ethiopia (Box 15)
- UCC Conference Bristol, Connecticut, 4/16/89 (Box 15)
- End of Prophesy (Box 15)
- Lori Adams Ordination (Box 15)
- Sewanee- Holy Week, 1987 (Box 15)
- Paper- 10th Annual Ethiopian Studies, Paris (Box 15)
- Knoxville, 2/19/89 (Box 15)
- Response to Perspectives Festschrift (Box 15)
- Bible Translation (Box 15)
- “The SBL: An Assessment of its’ Influence", 1880-1980 (Box 15)
- PSS- Introduction, John Knox Press (Box 15)
- Zechariah Commentary- Westminster (Box 15)
- 12 Prophets Commentary (Box 15)
- People of the book (Box 15)
- “Middle East Mosaic” (Box 15)
- Dharma World Article (Box 15)
- Brindisi Trip USAF (Box 15)
- Personalities of the Names between the Testaments (Box 15)
- Lancaster Seminary 4/8- 4/9 Ten Commandments (Box 15)
- Washburn University- Ezra Lectures (Box 15)
- Book Club Woodmont Christian Church 4/25 (Box 15)
- W.R. Harper- Notes (Box 15)
- Rock Creek Bible Society, 5/18/85 (Box 15)
- Prophets and Publicity Leadership-Vine Street, 7/28/85 (Box 15)
- Benton Chapel 10/11/85 Righteousness is enough (Box 15)
- University of Texas, 9/26/85 (Box 15)
- FelloFest-Vine Street, 9/25-10/23 (Box 15)
- Egyptian Trip (Box 15)
- Lectures on Egypt (Box 15)
- NCC Lecture (Box 15)
- Disciples of Christ District Meeting- Oklahoma City, OK, 10/19-10/21 (Box 15)
- How to Serve and How not to serve (Box 15)
- God’s Vindication and God’s Presence (Box 15)
- 3/6/ Leadership Nashville ’Diversity of Religion in Nashville>” (Box 15)
- Woman in Ministry in Black Churches (Box 15)
- ACLU- Scopes 60th Anniversary 4/18 (Box 15)
- Star Wars Research (Box 15)
- Vine Street- Christmas Communion Service, 1986 (Box 15)
- Middle East Lecture (Box 15)
- St. Olaf Preaching Conference (Box 15)
- Proclamation- Psalms (Box 15)
- Religion and Sex 4/4 (Box 15)
- 1st Presbyterian Church Series (Box 15)
- Pembroke State, 10/23-10/28 (Box 15)
- Sewanee Meditation 3/25 Tuesday (Box 15)
- Ezra in History, Tradition, and Legend- Chattanooga, TN SBL, 3/20-3/22 (Box 15)
- Great Decision 21 10:00-12:00am (Box 15)
- CSS, 2/10/88 (Box 16)
- Ten Commandments (Box 16)
- 2 Corinthians 5:14-21 Book (Box 16)
- Messianic Expectations of the Time of Jesus (Box 16)
- 1/31/99 Movement Builders (Box 16)
- Scribes-Introduction to the OT (Box 16)
- UTS April 7-9, 1989 (Union Theological Seminary (Box 16)
- Spire Critique of Compton’s Essay (Box 16)
- Evolution Article- TCH (Box 16)
- Harper’s Dictionary of Religious Education, 9/1/86 (Box 16)
- Ten Commandments Jan. 15, 1986- Oxford Companion to the Bible (Box 16)
- Harper’s Bible Commentary (Box 16)
- Harper’s Bible Commentary (Box 16)
- Harper’s Bible Commentary (Box 16)
- Harper’s Bible Commentary, 9/1/86 (Box 16)
- Ten Commandments- Dictionary of Pastoral Care and Counseling (Box 16)
- Ethics Articles (Box 16)
- Ten Commandment Encyclopedia of Religion (Box 16)
- Tithe (Box 16)
- Khierim Paper and Comments (Box 16)
- Hebrew Bible and it’s Modern Interpretations (Box 16)
- Thoughts on Ecumenism, Collegeville (Box 16)
- Religion of Israel Article- Vawter (Box 16)
- Vawter Festschrift (Box 16)
- Ten Commandments (Box 16)
- Myth and Ritual School- Encyclopedia of Religion (Box 16)
- Exodus- John Knox Press (Box 16)
- Exodus (Box 16)
- Ester- Textual Issues SBL (Box 16)
- Loose- Correspondence (Box 17)
- IFA (Box 17)
- Summary, Senate Actions 87-88 (Box 17)
- Senate Affairs Committee Review (Box 17)
- Review of Senate,86-87 (Box 17)
- Senate Report from Committee on Woman and Minorities (Box 17)
- Senate 87-88 (Box 17)
- Senate- South Africa (Box 17)
- Senate Affairs Committee (Box 17)
- Senate Consulting Committees (Box 17)
- Senate Affairs Committee 87-88 (Box 17)
- Review of Senate 83-84 (Box 17)
- Senate 87-88 (Box 17)
- Loose Correspondence (Box 18)
- Jones, A. Heath (Box 18)
- McNutt, Paula (Box 18)
- Matties, Gordon Henry- Ph.D. OT (Box 18)
- Loose Correspondence (Box 18)
- Barre, Lloyd (Box 18)
- Loose Correspondence (Box 18)
- Franklin, Paul (Box 18)
- Loose Correspondence(Half a Paige Box) (Box 18)
- Cook, Joan (Box 18)
- Heard Tribute, 4/28/82 (Box 18)
- SBL- 100th Anniversary Publications (Box 18)
- Loose Correspondence (Box 18)
- Bound Notes- Samuel Vol. 1 (Box 19)
- Bound Notes- Samuel Vol. 2 (Box 19)
- Bound Notes- Law- OT (Box 19)
- Bound Notes- OT Introduction- Samuel to Kings (Box 19)
- Bound Notes- OT Introduction- Hosea to Chronicles (Box 19)
- Bound Notes- Exodus Course #1 1-18 (Box 19)
- Bound Notes- Exodus Course #2 1-18 (Box 19)
- Bound Notes- Exodus Course #3 19-40 (Box 19)
- Bound Notes- OT Introduction- Exodus to Samuel (Box 19)
- Bound Notes- Genesis (Box 19)
- Seminar- Job (Box 20)
- Intertestamental Literature (Box 20)
- Exegesis 2504 Fall 87/88 (Box 20)
- Prophets #1 (Box 20)
- Greek- Ester (Box 20)
- Senior Seminar (Box 20)
- Summer Class 1982- Psalms (Box 20)
- 2503- Literature, Religion and Faith of Ancient Israel (Box 20)
- 3818- Aramaic Fall, 1987 (Box 20)
- 3802- Methods Fall, 1987 (Box 20)
- Post Exilic Literature DIV 3906 (Box 20)
- Exegesis- Hebrew Bible (Box 20)
- Advanced Hebrew Spring, 1987 (Box 20)
- 2 Esdras Seminar Fall, 1986 (Box 20)
- Prophets II Fall, 1986 (Box 20)
- Apocryphal- Pseudepigrapha- Sewanee Summer, 1987 (Box 20)
- Samuel 1 (Box 20)
- Intertestamental Literature (Box 20)
- Religion 110- Fall, 1981 (Box 20)
- Prophets- 7th Century, 6th Century- Jeremiah and Ezekiel (Box 20)
- Exodus- RSV Text (Box 20)
- Exodus- Sewanee (Box 20)
- Prophetic Proclamation- Isaiah- Spring, 1985 (Box 20)
- Theology of the Hebrew Bible (Box 20)
- Huntsville, Oct-Nov 1984 (Box 20)
- Psalms- General Course Fall, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
- Summer 1983 Prophets and Proclamation Sewanee (Box 20)
- GE’EZ-Spring, 1983 (Box 20)
- Law OT (Box 20)
- 1-2 Samuel (Box 20)
- Aramaic (Box 20)
- Sirach- Hebrew (Box 20)
- Bangalore (Box 21)
- Bicentennial (Box 21)
- Cumberland Presbyterian Theological Seminary (Box 21)
- Conference on Religion and Race (Box 21)
- Seminary Governance (Box 21)
- Divinity School Maintenance (Box 21)
- Koinonia – Vanderbilt Divinity Review (Box 21)
- “Eagle University”-Continuing Education (Box 21)
- Vanderbilt University Board of Trust (Box 21)
- Ecumenical Institute for Advanced Theological Studies: A five-year report, some plans for the future (Box 22, Folder 12)
- NEH – Official Documents (Box 22, Folder 13)
- EMML: Current Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 14)
- EMML: Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Redemptor Hominis (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Paul VI and Ecumenism (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Archeological Excursions and Files (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Christianity in the Holy Land (Box 22, Folder 19)
- EMML: Tantur- General Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 20)
- EMML: Tantur General Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Notre Dame 1976 Meeting on Tantur (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Romania Trip (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Tantur- Schedule (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Report on 1976 visit to Tantur (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Louvain- La- Neuve Meeting, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Expenses- Tantur (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Focolare (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Initial Proposal to Study Prayer at Tantur (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Pope John Paul II (Box 22, Folder 10)
- St. Catherine’s Monastery- New Finds (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Tantur- Forms (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Plans for Institute- General Memo, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Executive Committee Tantur (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Eastern Orthodoxy-Notes (Box 22, Folder 15)
- EMML: Publicity (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Ethiopic Manuscript with Hebrew Writing (Photo) (Box 22, Folder 17)
- EMML: New Grant Proposal (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Getatchew Haile (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Bulletins of Ethiopian Manuscripts Ed. S. Selassie- EMML (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Ethiopian Microfilming- General Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Jubilees Manuscripts (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Ethiopia- Development Commission-Friends of Eastern Orthodox Church (Box 23, Folder 23)
- EMML- NEH-Budget Revision (Box 23, Folder 24)
- EMML- Current Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 25)
- EMML- Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 1)
- EMML- Current Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Ethiopia- NEH Grant Request and Award H 5908 $1420 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Request for Matching Funds (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Initial Grant Request, 8/15/71 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Ethiopic Bible (Box 23, Folder 6)
- EMML- NEH Grant Request RO 4830 $4006 (Box 23)
- EMML- NEH H6356 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Patriarch’s Trip Correspondence, May 14-June 14 1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Patriarch’s Visit, May 14- June 14, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Minutes, Oct 11-133 1971, EMML Minutes of Meeting in Addis Ababa (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Minutes, Joint Consultation Meeting for Microfilming Ethiopian Church Manuscripts Addis Ababa, Apr 22-23, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- EMML-Minutes of Meeting in Addis Ababa, 2/10/72-2/13/72 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- EMML-Minutes of Meeting in Addis Ababa, 12/26/72-1/2/73 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- EMML-Minutes of Meeting of representatives of University Microfilms, INC. and EMML Ann Arbor, MI, 9/3/73-9/4/73 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- EMML-Minutes of 5th Meeting in Addis Ababa, 12/22/73-1/2/74 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- EMML-Minutes of 6th Meeting in Addis Ababa, 3/3/75-3/8/75 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- EMML-Minutes of 7th Meeting in Addis Ababa, 2/29/76-/3/5/76 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Confidential Report on Developments in EMML Project, 1975-76 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Minutes of Meeting-EMML and Related Bodies, 12/26/80-1/11/81 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Minutes- Macomber Visit, 12/2/79-/12/17/79 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- EMML-Minutes of 8th Meeting in Collegeville, MN, 12/28/77-/12/29/77 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Official Documents, EMML (Box 24, Folder 23)
- EMML- Early Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Ethiopian Microfilming Articles and Brochure (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Ethiopian Microfilming- Grant Requests, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- RSR: Editors and Editorial Advisory Committee (Box 24, Folder 27)
- RSR: Long Reviews in Plan and Progress (Box 24, Folder 1)
- RSR Expenses (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 3)
- RSR: Complete file of publications, Vol. 1-3, 1975-1977 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- RSR: Complete file of publications, Vol. 4-6, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Council of the Study of Religion: Report, Research, and Publication Committee, Oct 1978 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Council of the Study of Religion- Research and Publication Committee (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Translation of Kremers’ “Leidensgemeinschaft mit gott im Alten Testament” (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Spirit and Holy Spirit in the Bible (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Discipleship (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Ephraim’s appointment with Death (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Essential Christian Elements of a Scholarly Community (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Ezekiel 38-39 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Faith and Creation and Faith in the Time of Crisis (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Covenant in DSS (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Covenant Renewal at Qumran (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Creation in Bible (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Crisis in Ecumenical Relations- Chicago, 11/6/63 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Daniel 8 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Dimensions of Freedom in the OT (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Dead Sea Scrolls (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Oberlin Lectures on I Corinthians (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Prophets- 5 Lectures (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Covenant Code in Early Israel (Box 25, Folder 24)